



Mobile:+98 -9019920042

# **SUMMARY**

· Profile: Male, 28, Single

· Nationality: Iran

· Current Location: Iran, Khorasan, North **Current Position:** Freelance Developer

· Company: freelancer • Military Service: Completed

Salary expectation: 100000000 IRR, Per month

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

freelancer

♥ Iran, Khorasan, North, **Bojnourd** 

Freelance Developer

**Ē**Oct 2022 - Nov 2023



Matin

Frontend Web Developer May 2019 - Jun 2020



freelancer

**Bojnourd** 

Frontend Web Developer 📋 Jul 2018 - Apr 2019

# **EDUCATION**



2015 - 2019

-Engineering (Electrical/Electronic/Telecom) - Bachelor(BSc/BA)

Iran, Khorasan, North, **Bojnourd** 

### **SKILLS**

**Advanced JavaScript** 

Node.js **Basic**  tailwind css Intermediate

React Intermediate

Git Intermediate

HTML/CSS Advanced

# **LANGUAGES**

• Persian (Farsi) Native

• English Intermediate

# **ABOUT ME**

I'm a front-end developer with 2 years of experience. I specialize in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to create interactive and user-friendly web interfaces. Collaborating with designers and back-end developers, I build responsive websites and deliver seamless user experiences. I enjoy bringing ideas to life. It's nice to meet you!